we also can summarize stuff so we have this summarizer option over here if I
Come to the summarizer and try to let's say summarize this very article that chat GPT generated me
And as you see I paste so it also has its own modes so we can specify how we want to summarize so do we want to
summarize the entire article the entire article into a single paragraph do we want to summarize in
bullet points or do we have a custom mode for that and these are all doable so let's go with the
paragraph thing or let's go with the bullet points it will be more fun I assume right and if I wait a
little bit I will be able to click on the summarize button yes and see what we are going to
get 13 bullet points okay cool text is already summarized uh-huh yep learning French opens doors to
culture literature travel and personal growth identify your motivation for learning French such as
travel work and as you see it's doing its work perfectly right so I can also do it with
paragraph and if I try this one again I click summarize it says seven sentences and as you
see yes it's it has summarized the entire article into a single paragraph so it says learning
French is a fulfilling journey that opens doors to culture travel etc for beginners understanding
motivation is crucial be be it for travel study career or personal interest and as you see it has
summarized the entire of this long article into a single paragraph right